Hello hello hello friends welcome to your
own YouTube channel Belly us friends today
's video is for 8042 which
we keep doing with similar number Ajay Cylinder Engine
Insurance Customs
and after doing a lot of good work there is a
team of CSC Accuracy Limited,
their friend Mukesh of General Insurance keeps meeting them,
we keep making a lot of videos for this,
so today also we have got two very
beautiful gifts from such a person,
such a person
is close, we thank you very much for these gifts, we
thank you and try to have more
business, we can look at ICICI Lombard
and we will check as many insurances as possible, it is
very
good, I have done a lot of complete
insurance but no one has received so many
gifts as
beautiful as the ones
given in such shells, so let us see
what those gifts are,
take them, then we will tell you about the complete reason, the
first gift I
got is a beautiful bicycle chain with
such a share logo on it and
along with it the skin below  There is a button,
on pressing it there are some nice lighting effects,
you can see that it is quite
beautiful, this is a gift that
we have received from Aisei Umar, you
can see that it lights up like this, click on it, it is
very beautiful,
you can put it on your bike or your car and along with it the
second gift that we have received is a
beautiful pen, it is quite nice
and here its number is such that it is having
beautiful color with branding, it is a very beautiful pen,
this is also a very nice pen that we have received today from ICICI Lombard, we will keep
talking and it is very
nice, this is a dual [ __ ] pen from Spain, that is, it has
two functions,
one works like a pen
while it helps us in writing
and the second role of it is that
I liked it very much, here
you can see that it has two
parts, the part below is its weapon,
we can use it, it will be useful in writing
and the point above is this app Android
username, you can use it here  But you must be
seeing its crown, this is its salvation,
here we can
use it to display it, you can see that it is
very nice, you can also do it in it, by
opening it from here you
can fill the percentage in it, it gets refilled, it
opens itself,
put the centrifuge in it with water and keep it in your text,
work and send a percentage, you
can use it, so this is a very beautiful satin
pen which we got today from ICICI Lombard
and I have told you about the other key chain, the
same is a very beautiful key chain, so
this is a very beautiful sapphire
pen and also a sanitizer,
this is very nice to me,
thanks for this beautiful gift, ITI
number team, do a
great job and you can also
get all these gifts from ICC, you
just need to make palce and
get gifts, I hope you liked the video, if you
liked the video then definitely like, share and
subscribe to our channel